domainindia.org 2015-10-17

# Privacy Policy - Domain India

* * *

#### Privacy Policy

Last Revised: January 06, 2012.

This privacy statement describes how Domain India collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: http://www.domainindia.org/. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

##### Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password

If you are registering on behalf of your organization, your company’s name, mailing address, and other company information

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. 

##### We use this information to

  * Respond to customer service & offer requests
  * Administer your account
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts

##### Choice/Opt-Out

You may choose to stop receiving our emails by logging into your account and updating your notification selections or you can contact us at admin@domainindia.org  
We enable you to create an account, and share information such as messages, offers, & requests with others.

##### Information Obtained from Third Parties

If you provide us personal information about others (such as providing information about another individual to allow them access when creating a sub-account) we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

##### Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service (such as utilizing our ‘Live Chat’ feature). These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

##### We may also disclose your personal information

As required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,if Domain India is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information

to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

##### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

###### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use persistent cookie to store user id and session cookie to store different master ids. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

we use persistent cookie to store user id and session cookie to store different master ids.

##### Tracking Technologies &Third Party Cookies

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers are not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

We use Google Analytics, a third-party tracking service, which uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about our visitors to our site in the aggregate to capture usage and volume statistics. Some of our business partners (e.g., Google Analytics) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Domain India only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third-party. 

We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.

##### Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Domain India. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

##### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at admin@domainindia.org

##### Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, you may login to your account or contact us directly at admin@domainindia.org

##### Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

##### Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:

  * ##### Domain India

  * 2D, Thamarai Block , Shakthi Green Valley,
  * Near TKT Mill Bus Stop,
  * Palladam Road, Tirupur, Tamil Nadu, India- 641605.
